adparlor.com 2019-12-13

# Privacy Policy | AdParlor

Effective May 25, 2018

**This Policy may change from time to time.   Please check back for updates.**

AdParlor Media, Inc. (“AdParlor”, “we”, or “us”) respects and protects the privacy of consumers. This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) describes what information we collect, how we use that information, and some of your privacy rights regarding that information.

* * *

## Collection of Information and Your Privacy Rights

_**What information we collect and how we collect it.**_

AdParlor does not collect or retain the following consumer information: race, religion, sexual orientation, health, social security number (or other government issued identifying number), insurance plan number, financial account number, information relaying real-time location data (e.g. through GPS or other location-based services), or information about past, present or future health or medical condition. Occasionally, AdParlor may receive consumer information, such as email addresses, names, physical addresses, and phone numbers from its advertising clients in connection with specific advertising campaigns. This consumer information is not retained by AdParlor and is deleted following completion of the applicable campaign. It is never sold or shared with third parties not involved in the campaign.

AdParlor collects user submitted information such as name, email and password data to authenticate users, authenticate its commercial users, (AdParlor accounts and account services are available only to advertisers; they are not available to consumers), and to send notifications to those users relating to the AdParlor service. This information is not shared to anyone and is used by AdParlor so we can customize your experience and protect the security of your account.  
We may also use a user’s email address to send updates, a newsletter or news regarding  
Adparlor’s services.

AdParlor may also collect information from business partners, such as advertisers and agencies, on AdParlor’s website or self-service product offerings as necessary to provide services to those business partners. This may include, but is not limited to, names, email addresses, phone numbers, physical addresses, and other information provided by business partners to AdParlor through such a website or product offering (“Business Information”). Such information may be used and shared as necessary to perform AdParlor’s services for those business partners.

AdParlor logs IP address, date/time stamp, aggregate user data, and browser type, from users and visitors to its sites. This data is used to manage the websites, track usage and improve the website services. This non-personally-identifiable information may be shared with third-parties to provide more relevant services and advertisements to AdParlor’s account holders. User IP addresses are recorded for security and monitoring purposes.

We may use cookies when you use our services. In addition, AdParlor uses cookies in connection with consumers visiting the web pages of social media sites where we provide services to our account holders; however, the data we collect in connection with consumers is used for tracking clicks and conversions. Advertisers or other parties using our Services may use cookies or other means to track consumers over time across different websites. The use of such information collected by other parties is covered by those parties’ respective privacy policies. Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer’s hard drive by our servers to identify your computer to our servers. You can also disable cookies or otherwise manage them through tools provided with your browser software and with third-party software packages, or not use the features that require cookies.

Adparlor and/or its partners reserve their rights to use cookies to track individual responses or views of advertisements, and use this information to help predict what other advertisements may be of interest to consumers and enable the receipt of customized advertisements or content. These cookies contain no personally identifiable information. The cookies may reflect de-identified demographic or other data linked to data you voluntarily have submitted to us, such as your email address, that we may share with any third party, solely in hashed, non-human readable form. To learn about how you can opt-out of the receipt of cookies, please visit <http://www.aboutads.info/> choices and to learn more about cookies in general, please visit [http://www.cookiecentral.com](http://www.cookiecentral.com/). See more information about changing cookie preferences below in Use of Information and User Data section of policy.

We do not knowingly collect information about minors under the age of 13. MINORS UNDER THE AGE OF 13 SHOULD NOT PROVIDE OR SUBMIT ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION, INCLUDING THEIR EMAIL ADDRESS, TO ADPARLOR. If Adparlor is notified it has information about a minor under the age of 13, that information will be promptly deleted from our database. Minors are not permitted to open accounts with Adparlor.

AdParlor utilizes third party services to help optimize the performance of AdParlor.com. As of the date of this Privacy Policy, those services include: HubSpot, DoubleClick, Google Analytics, HotJar, Google AdWords, LinkedIn, and Facebook. This list may change from time to time. These third party services collect data through their own tracking methodologies that are not within the control of AdParlor. To opt out of these methodologies, you should not visit AdParlor.com, and follow the cookie removal instructions for your applicable browser and device. You can learn more about the data they collect and how they use that data by visiting the websites and privacy policies of these third parties.

* * *

## Use of Information and User Data

_**How we use and share the information we collect.**_

Except as otherwise described in this privacy policy, AdParlor will not disclose personal information to any third party unless we believe that disclosure is necessary: (1) to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other legal process received by AdParlor, whether or not a response is required by applicable law; (2) to enforce the AdParlor Terms of Use Agreement or to protect our rights; or (3) to protect the safety of members of the public and users of the service.

AdParlor reserves the right to transfer personal information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of AdParlor or substantially all of its assets to that successor in interest. AdParlor may also transfer information it collects to affiliated entities, parent companies, or subsidiaries, in AdParlor’s Discretion. For more information see the “Changes in Our Privacy Policy” section below.

_**How we store and protect the information we receive.**_

AdParlor user accounts are secured by user-created passwords and AdParlor takes certain precautions to ensure that user account information is kept private. We use reasonable measures to protect user information that is stored within our database, and we restrict access to member information to those employees who need access to perform their job functions, such as our customer service personnel and technical staff. Please note that we cannot guarantee the absolute security of member account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of member information at any time. For any additional information about the security measures we use on AdParlor, please contact us at [privacy at adparlor.com](mailto:privacy@adparlor.com).

* * *

## Privacy Practices of Third Parties

_**Third party privacy policies and use of cookies.**_

AdParlor and its services may link to other applications and may link to other sites, and third parties may collect data through its website. AdParlor is not responsible for the privacy policies, cookie usage, and/or other practices on or in connection with applications or websites controlled by third parties, as such practices may be used by third parties to track online activities over time across different websites. When linking to another site a user should read the privacy policy stated on that site. Our privacy policy only governs information collected by AdParlor. For more information on cookies and how you may be able to control their usage, we suggest visiting [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

* * *

## AdParlor Cookie Banners & Notifications

_**The following banners and notifications are placed on our website to inform users of actions surrounding our privacy and cookie policy online.**_

**INFORMATIONAL BANNER:** This banner informs users of AdParlor.com about updated changes to our privacy notes and cookie policy. By selecting “I accept” or not clicking on this banner, you agree to our site’s cookie and privacy policies. We encourage you to review our policies on this page.

**OPT-IN BANNER:** This banner informs users of AdParlor.com about updated changes to our privacy and cookie policy. If you would prefer that we not collect information that may be used to help determine which advertisements to serve you, select “Decline” from this banner. By selecting “I accept”, you agree to our site’s cookie and privacy policies. We encourage you to review our policies on this page.

**CONTACT FORM CHECKBOXES:** We have implemented checkboxes in our Hubspot collection forms on the bottom of each AdParlor page. By ticking the checkbox “I agree to receive other communications from AdParlor.”, you consent to us contacting you about our products and services, as well as other content that may be of interest to you. By ticking the checkbox “I agree to allow AdParlor to store and process my personal data.*”, you consent to us storing your personal data from our submission form on Hubspot.

* * *

## How You May Exercise Your Privacy Rights

_**Account deletion**_

To completely and permanently delete a user account, a user may contact us by postal mail at the following address: __

AdParlor Delete Account  
1209 King St. West  
Suite 100  
Toronto, ON M6K 1G2  
Canada

Or by sending email to [privacy@adparlor.com](mailto:privacy@adparlor.com) subject “DELETE ACCOUNT” — please note that the email must come from the account you wish to delete.

If you would like access to personal information we may have about you in our files, to correct, update, or to have us delete it, or would like to notify us of your choice to opt out of the sharing of any of your personal information, please contact us at the email address above or physical address at the end of this Privacy Policy.

Please note that, notwithstanding any requests otherwise, Business Information may be retained by us as necessary for business or legal purposes.

## More Information

_**Changes in our Privacy Policy**_ ** **

From time to time we may make changes to our privacy policy. If we make changes, we will post them on our site to make users aware of what the changes are so users will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and when we may disclose it. A user is bound by any changes to the policy when she or he uses the site after those changes have been posted.

_**Additional resources and contact information.**_ ** **

AdParlor is a wholly-owned subsidiary of V2 Ventures Group, LLC.  For more information about protecting your privacy, you may wish to visit [www.netcoalition.com](http://www.netcoalition.com/), and [www.privacyalliance.org](http://www.privacyalliance.org/).  We reserve the right to update this Policy at any time by re-publishing it to this website with a new effective date.

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of AdParlor, or your dealings with this Web site, please contact us at: [privacy@adparlor.com](mailto:privacy@adparlor.com) or at:

AdParlor Media, Inc.  
300 E. 39th Street  
Suite 5E  
Kansas City, MO 64111
